# **About Me**

I am an inquisitive and diligent worker with management and consulting experience. I have a passion for problem solving and learning. Consulting has taught me to live in the growth mindset where I strive to be better everyday. I strive to work for an organization that pushes me forward and values growth.

# Skills

React

Javascript

**NextJs** 

Tailwind

Python

Git

SQL

**Express** 

Ruby

Ruby on Rails

# **Contact**



+718-510-4672



stephenburnett714@gmail.com



www.stephenburnettportfolio.surge.sh



**Greater New York Area** 

# Stephen Burnett

# **Operations Manager**

# **Experience**

### Operations Manager

#### 2021 - 2022 | Hummingbird Telecom

- Manage three crews for a fiber installation company.
- Map and plan daily routes for the crews.
- Execute billing tasks and store information in the companies database.
- · Attain and training new employees.
- Coordinate the purchasing, maintenance, repair, inventory, transportation and storage of equipment.
- Create daily reports for completed work.
- Created a script in python using gspread that eliminated an hour of daily work.

#### **Business Analyst**

#### 2013 - 2021 | The Accela Group

Provided financial modeling, merger and acquisition analysis and client support services for financial advisory firm that focused on the development of start-up and early stage ventures.

Worked with a start up IT firm, Soromma Technologies, which focused on security and cloud services. Lead the efforts for:

- Identifying Technical Staff
- · Leading teams to develop web and mobile apps
- · Acquiring certifications

# Software Engineering Immersive

#### 2019 - 2020 | General Assembly

Full time fellow in Software Engineering Immersive program that include over 400 hours of professional training over 12 weeks. Education: Git, GitHub, Command Line, JS, CSS, HTML, React, Ruby, Ruby on Rails, SQL and Express.

## **Education**

#### 2020 | General Assembly

• Software Engineering Immersive

#### 2008 - 2012 | Misericordia University

• B.S. Heathcare Management